Guide to the Benjamin Sussman Papers, 1940-1995
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- H: Industries, Occupations, (19 boxes)
  - H-4700: Stamps (Box 24)
  - H-4800: Storage/moving (Box 24)
  - H-4900: Stationary/office supplies (Box 24)
  - H-5000: Swimming pools (Box 24)
  - H-5100: Business systems and equipment, general (Box 24)
  - H-5101: Personalities, general (Box 24)
  - H-5102: Historical, general (Box 24)
  - H-5103: Stationary, general (Box 24)
  - H-5104: Pens/pencils (Box 24)
  - H-5105: Calendars (Box 24)
  - H-5106: Office accessories (Box 24)
  - H-5107: Furniture systems (Box 24)
  - H-5108: Office design (Box 24)
  - H-5109: Typewriters, general (Box 24)
  - H-5110: Typewriter manufacturers (Box 24)
  - H-5111: Calculators (Box 24)
  - H-5112: Cash registers (Box 24)
  - H-5113: Electronic office, general (Box 24)
  - H-5114: Electronic office, management (Box 24)
  - H-5115: Electronic office, training (Box 24)
  - H-5116: Copiers (Box 24)
  - H-5117: Computers, general (Box 24)
  - H-5118: Software (Box 24)
  - H-5119: Services (Box 24)
  - H-5120: Suppliers (Box 24)
  - H-5121: Peripherals (Box 24)
  - H-5122: Industry, general (Box 24)
  - H-5123: Retailing (Box 24)
  - H-5124: Electronic mail, communications (Box 24)
  - H-5125: Lasers/microwaves (Box 24)
  - H-5126: Companies, general (Box 24)
  - H-5127: Foreign (Box 24)
  - H-5128: Burroughs (Box 24)
  - H-5129: Data General (Box 24)
  - H-5130: Digital (Box 24)
  - H-5131: Exxon (Box 24)
  - H-5132: Hewlett Packard (Box 24)
  - H-5133: Honeywell (Box 24)
  - H-5134: IBM (Box 24)
  - H-5134: Kodak (Box 24)
  - H-5135: 3M (Box 24)
  - H-5135: NCR (Box 24)
  - H-5136: Texas Instrument (Box 24)
  - H-5137: Victor (Box 24)
  - H-5138: Wang (Box 24)
  - H-5139: Xerox (Box 24)
  - H-5200: Telephone/telegraph, general (Box 24)
  - H-5201: Telephone, historical (Box 24)
  - H-5202: Telephone, foreign (Box 24)
  - H-5203: Phone companies, general (Box 24)
  - H-5204: Bell System (Box 24)
  - H-5205: Western Electric (Box 24)
  - H-5206: AT&T (Box 24)
  - H-5207: ITT (Box 24)
  - H-5208: Pacific Tel & Tel (Box 24)
  - H-5209: General Telephone (Box 24)
  - H-5210: Private phone systems (Box 24)
  - H-5211: Business communication, general (Box 24)
  - H-5212: Equipment, general (Box 24)
  - H-5213: Services, general (Box 24)
  - H-5214: Rates (Box 24)
  - H-5215: Telegraph, historical (Box 24)
  - H-5216: Companies, general (Box 24)
  - H-5217: Postal Telegraph (Box 24)
  - H-5218: Western Union (Box 24)
  - H-5219: Singing Telegrams (Box 24)
  - H-5300: Tobacco, general (Box 24)
  - H-5301: Cigars (Box 24)
  - H-5302: Cigarettes (Box 24)
  - H-5303: Pipes/pipe tobacco (Box 25)
  - H-5400: Toy/games, general (Box 25)
  - H-5500: Transportation, general (Box 25)
  - H-5501: Horse-drawn vehicles (Box 25)
  - H-5502: Railroads/trolleys, pre-1910 (Box 25)
  - H-5503: Railroads/trolleys, post-1910 (Box 25)
  - H-5504: Urban transit, general (Box 25)
  - H-5505: Taxis (Box 25)
  - H-5506: Trucking (Box 25)
  - H-5507: Warehousing, traffic (Box 25)
  - H-5600: Travel/resorts, general (Box 26)
  - H-5700: Vending machines (Box 26)
  - H-5800: Watches/clocks (Box 26)
  - H-5900: Water supply (Box 26)
  - H-9000: Automotives, general (Box 26)
  - H-9001: Personalities, general (Box 26)
  - H-9002: Automotive humor (Box 26)
  - H-9003: Consumer studies, general (Box 26)
  - H-9004: Feminine market (Box 26)
  - H-9005: Advertising, current (Box 26)
  - H-9006: Advertising ethics (Box 26)
  - H-9007: Automotive media, general (Box 26)
  - H-9008: Automotive trades (Box 26)
  - H-9009: Enthusiast publications (Box 26)
  - H-9012: Broadcast (Box 26)
  - H-9013: Automotive P/R (Box 26)
  - H-9014: Vintage advertising, general (Box 26)
  - H-9015: Factory merchandising (Box 26)
  - H-9016: Factory-consumer relations (Box 26)
  - H-9017: Dealer recruitment (Box 26)
  - H-9018: Dealer franchises (Box 26)
  - H-9020: Co-op programs (Box 26)
  - H-9021: Dealer councils (Box 26)
  - H-9022: Dealer associations, general (Box 26)
  - H-9023: Dealer advertising, general (Box 26)
  - H-9024: Dealer merchandising, general (Box 26)
  - H-9025: Dealer merchandising, facilities (Box 26)
  - H-9026: Auto shopping centers (Box 26)
  - H-9027: Discount, auction, etc. (Box 26)
  - H-9028: Financing (Box 26)
  - H-9029: N.A.D.A. (Box 26)
  - H-9030: Service, general (Box 26)
  - H-9031: Warranties (Box 26)
  - H-9032: Service training (Box 26)
  - H-9033: Service promotion (Box 26)
  - H-9034: Diagnostic centers (Box 26)
  - H-9035: Non-dealer services, general (Box 26)
  - H-9036: Used cars, general (Box 26)
  - H-9037: Used car merchandising (Box 27)
  - H-9038: Factory support, used cars (Box 27)
  - H-9039: Used car service (Box 27)
  - H-9040: Used car warranties (Box 27)
  - H-9041: Used car ethics (Box 27)
  - H-9042: Car rentals, miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - H-9043: Car leasing, general (Box 27)
  - H-9044: Fleet leasing (Box 27)
  - H-9045: U.S. manufacturing, general (Box 27)
  - H-9046: American motors, general (Box 27)
  - H-9047: AMC, through WWII (Box 27)
  - H-9048: AMC products (Box 27)
  - H-9048a: Kaiser Jeep / Willys (Box 27)
  - H-9049: Dealer associations (Box 27)
  - H-9050: Chrysler Corp., general (Box 27)
  - H-9051: Chrysler Corp., through WWII (Box 27)
  - H-9052: Chrysler/Imperial (Box 27)
  - H-9053: Dodge Division (Box 27)
  - H-9054: Plymouth Division (Box 28)
  - H-9055: De Soto (Box 28)
  - H-9056: Dealer associations (Box 28)
  - H-9057: Ford Motor Co., general (Box 28)
  - H-9058: Ford, through WWII (Box 28)
  - H-9059: Lincoln (Box 28)
  - H-9060: Mercury (Box 28)
  - H-9061: Ford Division (Box 28)
  - H-9062: Edsel (Box 28)
  - H-9063: Dealer associations (Box 28)
  - H-9064: General Motors, general (Box 28)
  - H-9065: GM, through WWII (Box 28)
  - H-9066: Buick Division (Box 28)
  - H-9067: Cadillac Division (Box 28)
  - H-9068: Chevrolet Division (Box 28)
  - H-9069: Oldsmobile Division (Box 28)
  - H-9070: Pontiac Division (Box 28)
  - H-9071: Dealer associations (Box 28)
  - H-9077: U.S. companies/products, misc. (32 folders) (Box 28)
  - H-9090: Custom cars, general (Box 28)
  - H-9091: Customs, U.S. (Box 28)
  - H-9092: Customs, foreign (Box 28)
  - H-9093: U.S. classics, antiques (Box 28)
  - H-9094: Foreign classics (Box 28)
  - H-9095: Classics/antiques, general (Box 28)
  - H-9096: Museums, collections (Box 28)
  - H-9097: Vintage car clubs (Box 28)
  - H-9098: Vintage aftermarket (Box 28)
  - H-9099: Restoration, general (Box 28)
  - H-9100: Antique oddities (Box 28)
  - H-9101: Austin-Healey (Box 28)
  - H-9102: Bentley (Box 28)
  - H-9103: Cortina/English Ford (Box 28)
  - H-9104: Jaguar (Box 28)
  - H-9105: Lotus (Box 28)
  - H-9106: MG (Box 28)
  - H-9107: Morris (Box 28)
  - H-9108: Rolls Royce (Box 28)
  - H-9109: Rover (Box 28)
  - H-9110: Sunbeam (Box 28)
  - H-9111: Triumph (Box 28)
  - H-9112: British Leyland/BMC (Box 28)
  - H-9113: Rootes Group, general (Box 29)
  - H-9114: Misc. British (Box 29)
  - H-9115: Amphicar (Box 29)
  - H-9116: BMW (Box 29)
  - H-9117: DKW (Box 29)
  - H-9118: Mercedes/Benz/Daimler (Box 29)
  - H-9119: Messerschmitt (Box 29)
  - H-9120: NSU (Box 29)
  - H-9121: Opel (Box 29)
  - H-9122: Porsche/Audi (Box 29)
  - H-9123: Volkswagen (Box 29)
  - H-9124: Misc. German (Box 29)
  - H-9125: Datsun (Box 30)
  - H-9126: Honda (Box 30)
  - H-9127: Mazda/product (Box 30)
  - H-9127a: Mazda/general (Box 30)
  - H-9128: Subaru (Box 30)
  - H-9129-9131: Toyota (Box 30)
  - H-9132: Misc. Japanese (Box 30)
  - H-9133: Citroen (Box 30)
  - H-9134: Peugeot (Box 30)
  - H-9135-9136: Renault (Box 30)
  - H-9137: Simca (Box 30)
  - H-9138: Misc. French (Box 30)
  - H-9139: Alfa Romeo (Box 30)
  - H-9140: Ferrari (Box 30)
  - H-9141-9142: Fiat (Box 30)
  - H-9143: Lancia (Box 30)
  - H-9144: Pinifarina (Box 30)
  - H-9145: Vespa (Box 30)
  - H-9146: Misc. Italian (Box 30)
  - H-9147: Saab (Box 30)
  - H-9148: Volvo (Box 30)
  - H-9149: Misc. Swedish (Box 30)
  - H-9150: Misc. Australian (Box 30)
  - H-9151: Misc. Canadian (Box 30)
  - H-9152: Misc. Russian (Box 30)
  - H-9153: Misc. Foreign products (Box 30)
  - H-9154: Foreign manufacturing, general (Box 30)
  - H-9155: Import market, general (Box 30)
  - H-9186: Utility vehicles (Box 30)
  - H-9187: Commercial vehicles, general (Box 30)
  - H-9188: Buses (Box 30)
  - H-9189: Trucks, general (Box 31)
  - H-9190: Trucks, by manufacturer (4 folders) (Box 31)
  - H-9191: Trucks, parts and accessories (Box 31)
  - H-9193: Trucking associations (Box 31)
  - H-9194: Military vehicles, general (Box 31)
  - H-9195: Military market, general (Box 31)
  - H-9200: Styling, general (Box 31)
  - H-9201: Engineering, general (Box 31)
  - H-9202: Quality control (Box 31)
  - H-9203: Forecasts (Box 31)
  - H-9204-9207: Experimental (Box 31)
  - H-9208: Air cushion vehicles (Box 31)
  - H-9209: Electrics, general (Box 32)
  - H-9210: Steam, general (Box 32)
  - H-9211: Turbines, general (Box 32)
  - H-9212: Propane gas, etc. (Box 32)
  - H-9213: Air pollution, general (Box 32)
  - H-9214: Noise pollution, general (Box 32)
  - H-9215: Junk cars (Box 32)
  - H-9216: Insurance (Box 32)
  - H-9217: Legal, general (Box 32)
  - H-9218: Labor relations, general (Box 32)
  - H-9219: Training programs (Box 32)
  - H-9220: Road conditions, general (Box 32)
  - H-9221: Effect on environment (Box 32)
  - H-9222: Government (Box 32)
  - H-9223: Road signs (Box 32)
  - H-9224: Traffic control (Box 32)
  - H-9225: Motor vehicle laws (Box 32)
  - H-9226: Safety, general (Box 32)
  - H-9227: Government (Box 32)
  - H-9228: Safety equipment (Box 32)
  - H-9229: Safety and the driver (Box 32)
  - H-9230: Drugs and driving (Box 32)
  - H-9231: Safety re: imports (Box 32)
  - H-9232: O.E.M., general (Box 32)
  - H-9233-9235: Aftermarket (Box 32)
  - H-9236: S.E.M.A. (Box 32)
  - H-9237: A.P.A.A. (Box 32)
  - H-9242: Petroleum, lubricant (Box 32)
  - H-9243: Additives (Box 32)
  - H-9244: Gasoline cans (Box 32)
  - H-9245: Tires, general (Box 32)
  - H-9246: Tire companies, general (Box 32)
  - H-9247: Tires, synthetic (Box 32)
  - H-9248: Tires, retreads (Box 32)
  - H-9249: Competition tires (Box 32)
  - H-9250: Kits, models, posters (Box 32)
  - H-9251: Polishes, cleaners (Box 32)
  - H-9252: Tools (Box 32)
  - H-9253: Instrumentation (Box 32)
  - H-9254: Radios, tapes (Box 32)
  - H-9255: Custom wheels (Box 32)
  - H-9260: Parts, general (Box 32)
  - H-9261: Accessories, general (Box 32)
  - H-9262-9264: High perfomance (Box 32)
  - H-9270: Car shows, general (Box 32)
  - H-9280: Car clubs, general (Box 33)
  - H-9281: Mobil economy run (Box 33)
  - H-9282: Union 76/Pure Oil trials (Box 33)
  - H-9290: Racing tie-ins (Box 33)
  - H-9291: Competition sponsorships (Box 33)
  - H-9292: Racing associations, general (Box 33)
  - H-9293: A.H.R.A. (Box 33)
  - H-9294: N.M.R.A. (Box 33)
  - H-9295: NASCAR (Box 33)
  - H-9296: N.O.R.R.A. (Box 33)
  - H-9297: S.C.C.A. (Box 33)
  - H-9300: Racing, general (Box 33)
  - H-9301: Sports car racing, general (Box 33)
  - H-9302: Indy 500 (Box 33)
  - H-9303: Monaco GP (Box 33)
  - H-9304: Le Mans (Box 33)
  - H-9305: Riverside GP (Box 33)
  - H-9306: Board tracks (Box 33)
  - H-9307: Stock car racing, general (Box 33)
  - H-9308: Riverside 500 (Box 33)
  - H-9309: Drag racing, general (Box 33)
  - H-9310: Salt Flats, speed trials (Box 33)
  - H-9311: Rallying, safaris, off road (Box 33)
  - H-9312: Speedways (Box 33)
  - H-9313: Racing personalities, general (Box 33)
  - H-9314: Racing personalities, alphabetically (14 folders) (Box 33)
- J: Automotive/Recreational Transportation, (4 boxes)
  - J-500: Motorcycles, general (Box 33)
  - J-501: Motorcycle manufacturing, general (Box 33)
  - J-502: Motorcycle media (Box 33)
  - J-503: Dealer merchandising (Box 33)
  - J-504: History, nostalgia (Box 33)
  - J-505: Racing, competition (Box 33)
  - J-506: Customs (Box 33)
  - J-507: Scooters, general (Box 33)
  - J-508: All-terrain cycles (Box 33)
  - J-509: Minicycles, general (Box 33)
  - J-515: Bridgestone (Box 33)
  - J-516: Bultaco (Box 33)
  - J-517: BSA (Box 33)
  - J-518: BMW (Box 33)
  - J-519: DKW (Box 33)
  - J-520: Ducati (Box 33)
  - J-521: Guzzi (Box 33)
  - J-522: Harley-Davidson (Box 33)
  - J-523: Hodaka (Box 33)
  - J-524: Honda (Box 33)
  - J-525: Jawa (Box 33)
  - J-526: Kawasaki (Box 33)
  - J-527: Montesa (Box 33)
  - J-528: Norton (Box 33)
  - J-529: Peugeot (Box 33)
  - J-530: Sears (Box 33)
  - J-531: Suzuki (Box 33)
  - J-532: Triumph (Box 33)
  - J-533: Yamaha (Box 33)
  - J-800: Recreational vehicles, general (Box 33)
  - J-801: RV media, general (Box 33)
  - J-802: RV market, general (Box 33)
  - J-803: Foreign (Box 33)
  - J-804: History, nostalgia (Box 33)
  - J-805: Humor (Box 33)
  - J-806: Travel tips (Box 33)
  - J-807: Campgrounds (Box 34)
  - J-808: Philosophy, advantages (Box 34)
  - J-809: Legislation, ecology (Box 34)
  - J-810: Safety (Box 34)
  - J-811: Security, thefts (Box 34)
  - J-812: Energy, fuel (Box 34)
  - J-813: Materials, construction (Box 34)
  - J-814: Projections, experimental (Box 35)
  - J-815: Customizing (Box 35)
  - J-816: Special applications (Box 35)
  - J-817: Associations, general (Box 35)
  - J-818: RVI/RVIA (Box 35)
  - J-819: TCA (Box 35)
  - J-820: RVA (Box 35)
  - J-821: RVDA (4 folders) (Box 35)
  - J-822: RV shows, general (Box 35)
  - J-823: OEM, general (Box 35)
  - J-824: Aftermarket, general (Box 35)
  - J-825: Towing systems (Box 35)
  - J-826: Air conditioning (Box 35)
  - J-827: Tires (Box 35)
  - J-828: Accessories, general (Box 35)
  - J-829: Service, general (Box 35)
  - J-830: Warranties (Box 35)
  - J-831: Insurance (Box 35)
  - J-832: Financing (Box 35)
  - J-833: Dealer recruitment (Box 35)
  - J-834: RV dealerships (Box 35)
  - J-835: Rentals (Box 35)
  - J-836: Electric RVs (Box 35)
  - J-837: Air cushion RVs (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - J-838: Dune buggies (Box 35)
  - J-839: 4-wheel drive, off-road (Box 35)
  - J-840: Snowmobilies, general (Box 35)
  - J-841: Snowmobilies, competition (Box 35)
  - J-842: Houseboats, trailer boats (Box 35)
  - J-843: Travel trailers (Box 35)
  - J-844: 5th wheelers (Box 35)
  - J-845: Camping trailers (Box 35)
  - J-846: Tent trailers, tops (Box 35)
  - J-847: Trailer towing (Box 35)
  - J-848: Motor homes, general (Box 35)
  - J-849: Mini motor homes, general (Box 35)
  - J-850: Motor homes, by name (14 folders) (Box 35)
  - J-851: Vans, conversions, general (Box 36)
  - J-852: Vans, conversions, by name (6 folders) (Box 36)
  - J-853: Pickup campers, general (Box 36)
  - J-854: Pickup campers, by name (Box 36)
  - J-855: Pickup campers, caps, general (Box 36)
  - J-856: RV manufacturers, misc. (Box 36)
  - J-856: RV manufacturers, misc., continued (20 folders) (Box 37)
- K: Humans, (1 box)
  - K-1: Men, heads (Box 37)
  - K-2: Men, standing (Box 37)
  - K-3: Men, sitting (Box 37)
  - K-4: Men, reclining (Box 37)
  - K-5: Men, hands, feet, etc. (Box 37)
  - K-6: Men, fashion (Box 37)
  - K-7: Women, heads (Box 37)
  - K-8: Women, standing (Box 37)
  - K-9: Women, sitting (Box 37)
  - K-10: Women, reclining (Box 37)
  - K-11: Women, kneeling (Box 37)
  - K-12: Women, figures, misc. (Box 37)
  - K-13: Women, hands, feet, etc. (Box 37)
  - K-14: Women, fashion (Box 37)
  - K-15: Couples (Box 37)
  - K-16: Groups, crowds (Box 37)
  - K-17: Family (Box 37)
  - K-18: Boys (Box 37)
  - K-19: Girls (Box 37)
  - K-20: Children, misc. (Box 37)
  - K-21: Babies (Box 37)
- L: Animals, (2 boxes)
  - L-1: Birds, misc. (4 folders) (Box 37)
  - L-2: Cats (Box 38)
  - L-3: Dogs (Box 38)
  - L-4: Horses/mules/donkeys (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - L-5: Cows, cattle (Box 38)
  - L-5a: Pigs (Box 38)
  - L-5b: Sheep (Box 38)
  - L-6: Wild animals, misc. (11 folders) (Box 38)
  - L-7: Snakes and reptiles (Box 38)
  - L-8: Prehistoric animals, misc. (Box 38)
  - L-9: Fish and amphibians, misc. (4 folders) (Box 38)
  - L-10: Insects, misc. (Box 38)
  - L-X: Animals, misc. (Box 38)
- M: Military, (3 boxes)
  - M-100: Military, general (Box 38)
  - M-101: Budgets/preparedness (Box 38)
  - M-102: Treaties/negotiations (Box 38)
  - M-103: NATO (Box 38)
  - M-104: Warsaw Pact (Box 38)
  - M-105: Protests/'Peace' movements (Box 38)
  - M-106: Pacifism/C.O.s (Box 38)
  - M-107: Unionization (Box 38)
  - M-115: Plans/logistics (Box 38)
  - M-116: Training/personnel (Box 38)
  - M-117: Draft/conscription (Box 38)
  - M-118: Women in military (Box 38)
  - M-119: Military schools/private (Box 38)
  - M-120: ROTC/NROTC (Box 38)
  - M-121: Misc. service schools (Box 38)
  - M-130: Military humor (Box 38)
  - M-131: Music/bands (Box 38)
  - M-132: USO/canteens (Box 38)
  - M-133: Military market/general (Box 38)
  - M-134: Military media (Box 38)
  - M-140: Veterans, general (Box 38)
  - M-141: Veterans organizations (Box 38)
  - M-142: Veterans Administration (Box 38)
  - M-143: POWs (Box 38)
  - M-144: Memorials/cemetaries (Box 38)
  - M-200: U.S. historical, general (Box 38)
  - M-201: Colonial conflicts, general (Box 38)
  - M-202: Revolutionary War (Box 38)
  - M-203: War of 1812 (Box 38)
  - M-204: Civil War (Box 38)
  - M-205: Spanish American War (Box 38)
  - M-206: 1914 Mexican Expedition (Box 38)
  - M-207: World War I (Box 38)
  - M-208: World War II (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - M-208: Pelelill (Box 39)
  - M-209: Korean War (Box 39)
  - M-210: Vietnam (Box 39)
  - M-211: Misc. U.S. conflicts (Box 39)
  - M-300: U.S. services, misc. (Box 39)
  - M-301: USMC, general (Box 39)
  - M-302: USMC personalities (Box 39)
  - M-303: USMC recruitment (Box 39)
  - M-304: USMC aviation (Box 39)
  - M-305: USMC schools (Box 39)
  - M-306: USMC reserves (Box 39)
  - M-315: U.S. Navy, general (Box 39)
  - M-316: USN personalities (Box 39)
  - M-317: USN recruitment (Box 39)
  - M-318: USN aviation (Box 39)
  - M-319: U.S. Naval Academy (Box 39)
  - M-320: USN reserves (Box 39)
  - M-330: U.S. Coast Guard, general (Box 39)
  - M-331: USCG personalities (Box 39)
  - M-332: USCG schools (Box 39)
  - M-340: U.S. Army, general (Box 39)
  - M-341: USA personalities (Box 39)
  - M-342: USA recruitment (Box 39)
  - M-343: US cavalry (Box 39)
  - M-344: USA aviation (Box 39)
  - M-345: U.S. Military Academy (Box 39)
  - M-346: National Guard/USA reserves (Box 39)
  - M-350: U.S. Air Corps/Air Force (Box 39)
  - M-351: ASAF personalities (Box 39)
  - M-352: USAF recruitment (Box 39)
  - M-353: Air Force Academy (Box 39)
  - M-360: Rapid deployment forces (Box 39)
  - M-400: Manufacturing/sales, foreign (Box 39)
  - M-401: Manufacturing/sales, U.S. (Box 39)
  - M-402: U.S. weaponry, general (Box 39)
  - M-403: Small arms, miscellaneous (Box 39)
  - M-404: Weaponry, historic (Box 39)
  - M-410: Chemical/biological, general (Box 39)
  - M-411: Nuclear warfare (Box 39)
  - M-412: Missiles, general (Box 39)
  - M-413: Laser technology (Box 39)
  - M-414: Misc. technology (Box 39)
  - M-500: Insignia/decorations, U.S. (Box 39)
  - M-501: Insignia/decorations, general (Box 39)
  - M-502: Heraldry (Box 39)
  - M-503: Warfare, historic, general (Box 39)
  - M-504: Armor, etc. (Box 39)
  - M-505: Memorabilia (Box 39)
  - M-506: Military miniatures (Box 39)
  - M-600: Foreign military, general (Box 39)
  - M-601: European military, general (Box 39)
  - M-602: Scandinavian (Box 39)
  - M-603: South American (Box 39)
  - M-604: Middle East (Box 39)
  - M-605: African (Box 39)
  - M-606: Far East/Asian (Box 39)
  - M-607: Canadian (Box 39)
  - M-608: China (Box 39)
  - M-609: Egypt (Box 39)
  - M-610: France (Box 39)
  - M-611: French Foreign Legion (Box 39)
  - M-612: Germany (Box 40)
  - M-613: Great Britain (Box 40)
  - M-614: Israel (Box 40)
  - M-615: Japan (Box 40)
  - M-616: Korea (Box 40)
  - M-617: Russia (Box 40)
  - M-618: Vietnam (Box 40)
  - M-700: Intelligence (Box 40)
  - M-701: OSS/CIA (Box 40)
  - M-702: ONI (Box 40)
  - M-703: U.S. agencies, misc. (Box 40)
  - M-704: Foreign agencies (Box 40)
  - M-705: OGPU/KGB (Box 40)
  - M-708: Film/TV/Stage, misc. (Box 40)
  - M-709: Books, general (Box 40)
  - M-710: Propaganda/disinformation (Box 40)
  - M-711: Press censorship (Box 40)
- N: Entertainment/Amusements, (4 boxes)
  - N-100: Entertainment, general (Box 40)
  - N-101: Marketing (Box 40)
  - N-102: Guilds, unions, general (Box 40)
  - N-103: Actors equity (Box 40)
  - N-104: S.A.G. (Box 40)
  - N-105: AFTRA (Box 40)
  - N-106: Agents/managers/casting (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous photos (no code) (Box 40)
  - N-108: Personalities, general (Box 40)
  - N-109: Personalities, A-D (3 folders) (Box 40)
  - N-109: Personalities, A-D (Box 41)
  - N-110-114: Personalities, E-Z (Box 41)
  - N-115: Critics (Box 41)
  - N-116: Circuses (Box 41)
  - N-117: Carnivals/fairs (Box 41)
  - N-118: Arcades, games (Box 41)
  - N-119: Expositions, general (Box 41)
  - N-120: Amusement/theme parks, general (Box 41)
  - N-121: Coney Island (Box 41)
  - N-122: Disneyland/Disney World (Box 41)
  - N-123: Knotts Berry Farm (Box 41)
  - N-124: Marineland (Box 41)
  - N-125: Magic Mountain (Box 41)
  - N-126: Sea World (Box 41)
  - N-127: Magic, magicians (Box 41)
  - N-128: Puppets (Box 41)
  - N-129: Mimes (Box 41)
  - N-130: Private entertainment (Box 41)
  - N-131: Costumes/props (Box 41)
  - N-132: Motion pictures, general (Box 41)
  - N-133: Movies, historical (Box 41)
  - N-134: Westerns (Box 41)
  - N-135: Studios, general (Box 41)
  - N-136: 20th-Century Fox (Box 41)
  - N-137: Disney Studios (Box 41)
  - N-138: MGM (Box 41)
  - N-139: Paramount (Box 41)
  - N-140: United Artists (Box 41)
  - N-141: Universal/MCA (Box 41)
  - N-142: Warner Bros. (Box 41)
  - N-143: Foreign studios (Box 41)
  - N-144: Production, general (Box 41)
  - N-145: Cinematography (Box 41)
  - N-146: Sound, color (Box 41)
  - N-147: Equipment, miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - N-148: Sets, back lots (Box 41)
  - N-149: Hollywood (Box 41)
  - N-150: Locations (Box 41)
  - N-151: Movie marketing (Box 42)
  - N-152: Exhibitors/theaters (Box 42)
  - N-153: Film rentals (Box 42)
  - N-154: Business films (Box 42)
  - N-155: Cassettes/tape (Box 42)
  - N-156: Movie piracy (Box 42)
  - N-157: Film expositions (Box 42)
  - N-158: Propaganda (Box 42)
  - N-159: Censorship/controversy (Box 42)
  - N-200: Television, general (Box 42)
  - N-201: TV, historical (Box 42)
  - N-202: TV, prognostication (Box 42)
  - N-203: TV technology, general (Box 42)
  - N-204: Satellites (Box 42)
  - N-205: Closed circuit (Box 42)
  - N-206: TV production, general (Box 42)
  - N-207: TV producers, general (Box 42)
  - N-208: Foreign TV production (Box 42)
  - N-209: TV receivers, general (Box 42)
  - N-210: Videodiscs, cassettes (Box 42)
  - N-211: Pay TV, CATV (Box 42)
  - N-212: Public broadcasting (Box 42)
  - N-213: FCC, licensing, general (Box 42)
  - N-214: TV networks (Box 42)
  - N-215: Syndication (Box 42)
  - N-216: Programming, general (Box 42)
  - N-217: Soaps (Box 42)
  - N-218: TV censorship, controversy (Box 42)
  - N-300: Radio, general (Box 42)
  - N-301: Radio, historical (Box 42)
  - N-302: Radio technology (Box 42)
  - N-303: Production (Box 42)
  - N-304: Radio receivers, general (Box 42)
  - N-305: Radio networks (Box 42)
  - N-306: Programming, general (Box 42)
  - N-307: Censorship, controversy (Box 42)
  - N-400: Stage, general (Box 42)
  - N-401: Stage, historical (Box 42)
  - N-402: Promotion, marketing (Box 42)
  - N-403: Theatres, general (Box 42)
  - N-404: Broadway (Box 42)
  - N-405: L.A. theater (Box 42)
  - N-406: Community theater, general (Box 42)
  - N-407: Foreign theater (Box 42)
  - N-408: Producing, production (Box 42)
  - N-409: Managers, bookers (Box 42)
  - N-410: Ballet (Box 42)
  - N-411: Shakesperean theatre (Box 42)
  - N-412: Chautauqua (Box 42)
  - N-413: Open air theater, general (Box 42)
  - N-414: Minstrel shows (Box 42)
  - N-415: Vaudeville, burlesque (Box 42)
  - N-416: Nightclubs (Box 42)
  - N-417: Topless, etc. (Box 42)